{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478604924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478604924"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478605126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478605126"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 7da25de6-63bc-4e3f-9f1a-e99804b90bf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478605291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478605291"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 7da25de6-63bc-4e3f-9f1a-e99804b90bf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478611159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478611159"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 7da25de6-63bc-4e3f-9f1a-e99804b90bf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478618262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478618262"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 7da25de6-63bc-4e3f-9f1a-e99804b90bf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478623595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478623594"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 7da25de6-63bc-4e3f-9f1a-e99804b90bf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478634779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478634779"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478640395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478640394"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478642005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478642005"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478644928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478644928"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478646537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478646536"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478649526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478649525"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478651127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478651126"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JICHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478653866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478653865"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JICHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478655490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478655489"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478658735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478658735"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478660356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478660356"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEKUNDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478664051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478664051"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEKUNDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478665669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478665668"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478669138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478669138"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478670764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478670763"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478676247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478676246"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478677875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478677874"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478680443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478680443"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" START_JIKONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478682088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478682088"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" START_JIKONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478683616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478683614"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478685631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478685630"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478685791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478685791"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 22c7d8a2-4b1e-4c32-b01d-600995cc2470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478698244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478698244"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478707264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478707264"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" START_JASHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478708717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478708717"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478710339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478710339"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478713489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478713488"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478715106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478715105"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478718013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478718012"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478719644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478719644"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JICHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478722269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478722269"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JICHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478723869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478723869"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478726264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478726264"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478727873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478727873"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEKUNDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478731572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478731572"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a5cba806-9fc9-4e2e-8795-cc9bd9d8002b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEKUNDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478913013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478913012"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d5dce0b9-d696-4cff-bcec-7b57c68c2dc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478954508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478954508"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d5dce0b9-d696-4cff-bcec-7b57c68c2dc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478999838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478999837"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d5dce0b9-d696-4cff-bcec-7b57c68c2dc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548478999905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548478999904"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d5dce0b9-d696-4cff-bcec-7b57c68c2dc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479006865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479006864"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d5dce0b9-d696-4cff-bcec-7b57c68c2dc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479012633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479012633"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d5dce0b9-d696-4cff-bcec-7b57c68c2dc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479024822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479024821"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d5dce0b9-d696-4cff-bcec-7b57c68c2dc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479066382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479066381"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479072065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479072065"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479098434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479098434"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479124246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479124246"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479153851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479153851"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479185755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479185755"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479216258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479216258"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_11"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479247278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479247278"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479278468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479278467"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479278559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479278558"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479285316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479285316"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479292565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479292565"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479307722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479307721"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479317091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479317090"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479324221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479324221"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548479331538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548479331538"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548482793900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548482793899"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548482819210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548482819209"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 33debb8d-8eb8-4576-8f82-4f5de056e828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548482819278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548482819278"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 1e238895-db08-41bc-ae52-bdd24b445efd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498597623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498597623"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 1e238895-db08-41bc-ae52-bdd24b445efd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498609519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498609519"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498617406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498617406"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-7-8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498623196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498623196"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-8-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498630791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498630791"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_8-7-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498639514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498639514"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-4-9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498652107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498652106"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-9-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498670486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498670486"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-1-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498696621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498696621"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-8-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498712486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498712486"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-8-0"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498719228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498719228"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_2-8-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498725894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498725894"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 64e356d9-42b8-4637-ab9e-f1b73116c3b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_8_2-8-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498736364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498736364"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498739006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498739005"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498740565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498740565"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498744546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498744545"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498746136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498746136"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498759964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498759964"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498761582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498761581"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498765765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498765764"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498767336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498767335"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498770947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498770947"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498772522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498772521"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498776625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498776625"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498778246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498778245"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498785192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498785192"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498786760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498786759"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498795530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498795530"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498797093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498797093"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498801604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498801603"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498803206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498803206"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498806687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498806686"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498808285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498808284"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498816174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498816174"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498817753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498817753"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498822121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498822121"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498823673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498823673"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498832208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498832208"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498833821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498833821"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498838986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498838986"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498840541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498840541"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498845010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498845009"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498846605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498846605"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498853818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498853818"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498855408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498855408"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498859710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498859710"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498861284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498861284"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498867333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498867333"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498868909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498868908"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498872470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498872470"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498874077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498874076"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KWAHERI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498880957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498880956"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KWAHERI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498882536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498882536"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498888969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498888969"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498890525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498890525"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITUNGUU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498896748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498896748"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITUNGUU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498898342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498898342"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KATIKATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498915272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498915271"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KATIKATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498916872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498916872"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498921209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498921209"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" c4c3715a-8f7c-48da-9ad7-d43915790dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498967993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498967993"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498970876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498970875"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498972425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498972425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498977090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498977090"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498978669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498978669"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498981366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498981366"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498982966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498982966"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498985783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498985783"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498987368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498987367"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498991288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498991288"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498992923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498992923"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548498999540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548498999539"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499001169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499001169"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499006741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499006741"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499008367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499008366"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499012525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499012525"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499012651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499012650"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 50dc62fa-6806-48d7-8229-f557b1b02b36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499043173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499043173"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499054122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499054122"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499055731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499055731"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499061351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499061351"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499063023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499063023"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499066538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499066537"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499068127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499068126"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499070917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499070917"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499072490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499072489"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499079640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499079639"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499081225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499081225"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499081413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499081413"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499081554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499081554"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 6bdf9c3d-4bf7-4c0a-acc7-19bf52b5984e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499093120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499093120"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499096706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499096706"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499098244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499098244"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499102454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499102453"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499104040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499104040"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499108260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499108260"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499109848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499109848"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499114158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499114158"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499115758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499115757"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499122704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499122703"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499124374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499124373"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499129445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499129445"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499131127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499131126"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499133767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499133767"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499135350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499135350"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499140485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499140485"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499142106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499142106"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499149599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499149598"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499151229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499151228"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499164636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499164635"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499166233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499166232"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499175989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499175989"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499177548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499177547"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499180915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499180915"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499182509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499182509"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499187301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499187301"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499188870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499188870"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499194043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499194043"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499195632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499195631"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499198781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499198780"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499200362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499200361"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499203362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499203362"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499205024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499205024"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499208757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499208757"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499210313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499210313"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499212649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499212649"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499214218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499214218"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548499220506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548499220506"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 96ae02ab-7376-4413-a644-7bd27f54a97f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500205793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500205792"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500219806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500219806"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500221383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500221383"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500229933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500229933"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500231556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500231555"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500234250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500234249"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500234370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500234370"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500240820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500240820"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500251977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500251976"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" d30da637-91fb-473a-b224-20045bf53a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500263649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500263647"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 1bc34037-4a83-405d-a4a5-7fdd65d28baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500264165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500264164"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 1bc34037-4a83-405d-a4a5-7fdd65d28baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500264971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500264970"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 1bc34037-4a83-405d-a4a5-7fdd65d28baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500267425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500267425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 1bc34037-4a83-405d-a4a5-7fdd65d28baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500267518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500267518"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 1bc34037-4a83-405d-a4a5-7fdd65d28baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500276886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500276886"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 1bc34037-4a83-405d-a4a5-7fdd65d28baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500288693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500288693"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500288866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500288866"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500289190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500289190"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500290333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500290333"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500291058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500291058"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500294309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500294309"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" ALASIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500294943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500294942"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500295738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500295738"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500296586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500296586"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500297532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500297531"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIOKOTA"," userResponse":" AKIOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500298215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500298215"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500301121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500301121"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUHUDIA"," userResponse":" ALISHUHUDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500301827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500301827"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIO"," userResponse":" TUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500302859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500302858"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500303039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500303039"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500303804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500303804"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500306917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500306917"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500307743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500307742"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISTARI"," userResponse":" MISTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500307807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500307807"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500308401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500308401"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500308980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500308980"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500309773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500309773"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500313223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500313223"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGUSHA"," userResponse":" ALIANGUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500313852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500313852"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500314522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500314522"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500317573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500317573"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500318466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500318466"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500319564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500319564"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500320743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500320743"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500324105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500324104"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500324496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500324495"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500325125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500325124"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500326337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500326337"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" WAMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500326996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500326996"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500328454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500328453"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500329311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500329310"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500332264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500332263"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500333235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500333235"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500334118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500334117"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500334785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500334785"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKA"," userResponse":" SHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500335824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500335823"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500337117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500337116"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANING"," userResponse":" INANING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500337129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500337129"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500338005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500338005"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500339098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500339098"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500341458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500341458"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500342215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500342215"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500343080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500343079"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500345138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500345138"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500345699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500345699"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500346484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500346483"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMWAGA"," userResponse":" ANAMWAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500346999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500346998"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500347794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500347794"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500348467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500348467"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500349325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500349325"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500352189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500352188"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500352996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500352996"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500354566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500354565"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUBALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIKUBALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500354795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500354795"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500355336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500355335"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500356144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500356143"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500356762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500356762"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500357824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500357822"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWAMINI"," userResponse":" WAKIMWAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500358320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500358320"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500360719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500360718"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUNDI"," userResponse":" VIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500361137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500361137"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500361686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500361685"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIWILI"," userResponse":" VIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500363052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500363052"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIBISHANA"," userResponse":" VILIBISHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500366498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500366497"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500367431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500367431"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500368170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500368167"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500368399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500368399"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500368998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500368997"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500369842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500369842"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKEA"," userResponse":" ALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500370021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500370021"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500370644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500370643"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500372491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500372490"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKOSEA"," userResponse":" MMEKOSEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500373269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500373269"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOTE"," userResponse":" NYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500376310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500376310"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500377138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500377138"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500377794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500377794"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500378404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500378403"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500378794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500378794"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500378992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500378992"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500379725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500379724"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500382578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500382578"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500383245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500383245"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500384091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500384090"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500384784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500384783"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500385567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500385567"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500388197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500388196"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500389387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500389386"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMJAWAHI"," userResponse":" HUMJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500390170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500390170"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500390955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500390955"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500393930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500393930"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500396315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500396315"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500396341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500396341"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500396353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500396353"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500396363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500396363"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500396373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500396373"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500396385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500396385"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500397253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500397253"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500398133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500398130"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500400993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500400992"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIULIZA"," userResponse":" WALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500401492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500401492"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500402242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500402241"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500403330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500403328"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500403743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500403743"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500404457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500404456"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500407526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500407525"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500408483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500408483"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500409225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500409224"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500409875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500409875"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500410785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500410784"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500413516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500413516"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500414319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500414319"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500415132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500415131"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500417746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500417745"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500418359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500418359"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500418932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500418932"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500419906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500419906"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500420799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500420799"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500421863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500421862"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEENDA"," userResponse":" AMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500422435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500422434"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500425094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500425092"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500425212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500425212"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500433628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500433628"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500442056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500442056"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500453063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500453063"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 55969b41-c74d-41c1-85f0-63c58497efc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500464184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500464184"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500466552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500466552"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500466993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500466993"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500467197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500467196"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500467710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500467710"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500470649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500470649"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NINASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500471248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500471248"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500471437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500471437"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500472228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500472228"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500474809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500474808"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500475582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500475582"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500478525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500478525"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500479769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500479768"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" NIMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500480219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500480218"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500481000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500480998"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" MSTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500483579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500483579"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500485028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500485028"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANANIIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500485477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500485477"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500487877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500487877"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500488240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500488240"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500489206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500489206"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500489695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500489694"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500490573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500490573"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" HUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500493490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500493490"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TWASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500494353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500494353"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500495030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500495030"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500496114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500496113"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500499450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500499449"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500499937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500499937"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" ALIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500500541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500500540"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500501124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500501124"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500502456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500502455"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ANAWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500502846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500502845"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500503553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500503553"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500506135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500506135"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" WATATAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500506929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500506929"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYAI"," userResponse":" MAYAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500507564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500507564"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500507918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500507917"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500511459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500511459"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500512165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500512165"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500513296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500513296"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUDI"," userResponse":" WANARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500514055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500514054"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500514610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500514609"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500518156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500518156"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" WANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500521095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500521095"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASIKIA"," userResponse":" NAWASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500521881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500521880"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIIMBA"," userResponse":" WAKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500522799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500522799"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500523634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500523634"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500524134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500524134"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500524422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500524422"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500525583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500525582"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500528278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500528277"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500528603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500528603"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAJA"," userResponse":" YAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500528859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500528859"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500529842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500529842"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500533265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500533265"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500534138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500534138"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPITA"," userResponse":" ANAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500535122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500535122"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500537377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500537377"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" YUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500538240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500538240"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHIFU"," userResponse":" NADHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500539035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500539035"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500541467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500541467"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500541920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500541920"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500542183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500542183"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500542827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500542827"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500543270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500543269"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500545940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500545940"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINAENDA"," userResponse":" VINAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500546915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500546915"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500547434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500547434"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500547906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500547906"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500550487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500550487"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500550944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500550944"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500551334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500551334"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500554568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500554567"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOTEMBEA"," userResponse":" ANAPOTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500557808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500557808"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500558438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500558437"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500559394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500559394"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" ANAUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500560203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500560201"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500560965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500560964"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500563685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500563685"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAPENDA"," userResponse":" NAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500564541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500564541"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500565429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500565429"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500567748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500567745"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500568562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500568562"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500568849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500568849"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500569684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500569684"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500570523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500570523"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500572685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500572684"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500574210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500574210"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVIPENDA"," userResponse":" UNAVIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500577401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500577401"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500579838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500579838"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500580808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500580808"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500581844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500581843"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPELEKA"," userResponse":" WANAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500582442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500582441"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500583037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500583037"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAO"," userResponse":" CHAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500583290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500583290"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500584192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500584192"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500585341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500585340"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500586161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500586160"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWANI"," userResponse":" VICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500586706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500586706"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAO"," userResponse":" MWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500588644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500588643"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500589311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500589310"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500590060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500590060"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEREVU"," userResponse":" WEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500593344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500593344"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500594088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500594087"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500595088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500595088"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASUKWA"," userResponse":" ANASUKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500595476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500595476"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500596018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500596018"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500598830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500598829"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAENDA"," userResponse":" ATAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500599415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500599415"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500599652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500599652"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500600454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500600454"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500601040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500601040"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500601803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500601802"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500602447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500602447"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500605561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500605560"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMECHOKA"," userResponse":" NIMECHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500606193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500606192"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500608825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500608825"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500609787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500609786"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIWEKA"," userResponse":" ANANIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500610577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500610577"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500611146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500611145"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500612845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500612844"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAPUMZIKE"," userResponse":" NIKAPUMZIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500615945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500615945"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAIMBA"," userResponse":" ANAIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500617230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500617230"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500617661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500617661"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500618491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500618491"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500620125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500620124"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USICHELEWE"," userResponse":" USICHELEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500621154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500621154"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500622221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500622221"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500622712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500622712"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500623213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500623213"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGO"," userResponse":" LANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500624162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500624161"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500626941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500626940"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500627619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500627619"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500628230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500628230"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500628488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500628487"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMI"," userResponse":" TUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500631521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500631521"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500631850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500631850"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500632825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500632825"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" ANAPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500635608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500635608"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUWA"," userResponse":" TUTAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500636356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500636355"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500636795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500636794"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500637581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500637581"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500640719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500640719"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500641091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500641090"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500641920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500641919"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500642851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500642851"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUKA"," userResponse":" WANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500643805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500643805"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500644609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500644609"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500647584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500647584"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500648235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500648235"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAFIKE"," userResponse":" WAFIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500649077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500649076"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500649745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500649745"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500650194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500650194"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500651005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500651005"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500654289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500654288"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500654813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500654812"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500655386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500655386"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500656040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500656040"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPULI"," userResponse":" VIPULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500657393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500657393"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500660052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500660052"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500661325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500661325"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALIVINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500662308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500662308"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500662631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500662631"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500664945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500664945"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500665647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500665646"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500666826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500666825"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITANUNUA"," userResponse":" NITANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500667470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500667470"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPULI"," userResponse":" VIPULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500668322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500668322"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" VINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500669191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500669190"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYANGU"," userResponse":" VYANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500669491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500669490"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500669749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500669749"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500670467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500670466"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500673671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500673670"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500674499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500674499"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANZA"," userResponse":" ANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500675186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500675186"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOKA"," userResponse":" KUCHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500675814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500675814"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500679039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500679039"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" NAMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500679579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500679578"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500680691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500680691"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500681162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500681162"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500682086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500682086"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500683494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500683493"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKUJA"," userResponse":" UNAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500685341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500685340"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUNASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500685942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500685942"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500686173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500686172"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500687127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500687127"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500690067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500690066"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOJA"," userResponse":" NGOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500693285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500693285"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASIKIA"," userResponse":" NINASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500693847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500693847"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500696474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500696473"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500697072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500697072"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500698089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500698089"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKUJA"," userResponse":" INAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500701126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500701126"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500701335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500701334"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500701934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500701934"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500702163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500702162"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500702824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500702824"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500703641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500703641"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500706604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500706603"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEKUJA"," userResponse":" IMEKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500707673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500707672"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUNIPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500708443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500708443"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500708652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500708651"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500709442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500709442"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500710348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500710347"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500714154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500714153"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" NIMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500715424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500715423"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500719544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500719544"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500722308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500722308"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500722420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500722420"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500729510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500729510"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500735598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500735598"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500743669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500743669"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500750406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500750406"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500767305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500767305"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500772558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500772558"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500779253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500779252"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500991757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500991756"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 9ceee33c-96b2-4b45-8563-90c9e62e4982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500991865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500991865"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a70e2b36-7a2d-4cfb-9f87-3025eae88652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAADUI"," userResponse":" MAADUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501007751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501007751"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" LAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501011466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501011466"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501013058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501013058"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501018879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501018879"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" START_LAINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501022939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501022939"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501024564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501024564"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501027464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501027464"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501029064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501029064"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501032056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501032056"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501033624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501033623"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMAU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501040419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501040419"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMAU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501042014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501042014"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501045260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501045260"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501047276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501047275"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501047384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501047384"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 5eba7b3f-d17c-4949-becd-736d3ab7b879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501083856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501083855"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501085358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501085358"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501087642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501087641"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501101975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501101975"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501115495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501115495"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501122539","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501122539"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501135437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501135436"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501144099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501144098"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501151568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501151567"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501256386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501256386"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 3a3ff96b-6c1f-4ab4-a24f-cdf6f3d1ee66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501256524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501256524"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 8c12ef8b-4e21-433e-bd83-3623d4dea793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501264472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501264471"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 8c12ef8b-4e21-433e-bd83-3623d4dea793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501271669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501271668"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 8c12ef8b-4e21-433e-bd83-3623d4dea793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501282676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501282676"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" da33acf4-f381-4f0c-b824-dc279b5332a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_A-L-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501286822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501286821"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" da33acf4-f381-4f0c-b824-dc279b5332a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_G-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501290172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501290171"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" da33acf4-f381-4f0c-b824-dc279b5332a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_N-Z-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501291651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501291651"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" da33acf4-f381-4f0c-b824-dc279b5332a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_L_N-Z-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501319671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501319670"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" da33acf4-f381-4f0c-b824-dc279b5332a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_L_N-Z-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501319812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501319812"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 4741ab83-ade1-4900-b6e1-f46ee360bc31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" MSTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501339347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501339346"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 4741ab83-ade1-4900-b6e1-f46ee360bc31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501359515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501359515"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501362764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501362764"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501364593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501364593"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501365219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501365219"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501366929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501366929"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501367425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501367425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501375871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501375871"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501382573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501382572"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501390764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501390764"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501406021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501406021"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501413647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501413645"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501424493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501424492"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501436202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501436202"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501443026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501443026"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501450840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501450840"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 14ea712c-7057-4952-845e-ff231da71a1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501460486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501460486"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501462691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501462690"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501464840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501464840"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501468050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501468050"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501470317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501470317"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501472608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501472608"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501475472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501475471"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501477689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501477689"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501479891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501479891"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501483834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501483834"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501493330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501493330"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501495994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501495992"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501496138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501496137"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" a176df52-85de-4525-846a-bee067548d43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501537358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501537358"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 36159459-c4c2-477b-919f-4b6d760392d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501540749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501540748"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 36159459-c4c2-477b-919f-4b6d760392d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501543446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501543446"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 36159459-c4c2-477b-919f-4b6d760392d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501576647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501576647"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 36159459-c4c2-477b-919f-4b6d760392d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501576989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501576988"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" 36159459-c4c2-477b-919f-4b6d760392d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijitolea kukomesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOMESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOMESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501590918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501590918"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" acb6ccad-a856-4930-820b-c3d559e8188f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501619105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501619105"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" acb6ccad-a856-4930-820b-c3d559e8188f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501619659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501619659"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" acb6ccad-a856-4930-820b-c3d559e8188f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501638847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501638847"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20190125_190456"," gameId":" da2e254b-fefa-4ea1-8dde-7fe3ebeca0f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}